<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Case Studies &#8211; dksmith  |  developer</title>
	<atom:link href="https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/case-studies/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 22:10:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.0.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/cropped-dks-icon-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Case Studies &#8211; dksmith  |  developer</title>
	<link>https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Accelerate Marketing</title>
		<link>https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/case-studies/accelerate-marketing/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 21:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniel]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/?post_type=case_studies&#038;p=28</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Accelerate Marketing had a fully functioning WordPress site that they needed upgraded and customized. Using the provided PSDs, I was able to create custom page templates, replicate the desired designs, and create custom 404, contact,[...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4>Accelerate Marketing had a fully functioning WordPress site that they needed upgraded and customized. Using the provided PSDs, I was able to create custom page templates, replicate the desired designs, and create custom 404, contact, and services pages. I also installed and customized plugins to add functionality and appeal to the site. </h4>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wellness Program Collateral</title>
		<link>https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/case-studies/wellness-program-collateral/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 23:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniel]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/?post_type=case_studies&#038;p=119</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Veda Salon &#038; Spa implemented a Wellness Program for their services and needed a flyer and mirror talker to promote the program. Using Photoshop and their existing brand guidelines I was able to create a[...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4>Veda Salon &#038; Spa implemented a Wellness Program for their services and needed a flyer and mirror talker to promote the program. Using Photoshop and their existing brand guidelines I was able to create a clean, concise, and eye-catching flyer. This collateral has brought a lot of attention and new members to the program. </h4>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jubilee Austen</title>
		<link>https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/case-studies/jubilee-austen/</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 21:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniel]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/?post_type=case_studies&#038;p=100</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Jubilee Austen provided a Photoshop mockup that she desired to be turned in to a clean and simple portfolio website. I replicated this website from scratch using the provided PSD. The website was designed using[...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4>Jubilee Austen provided a Photoshop mockup that she desired to be turned in to a clean and simple portfolio website. I replicated this website from scratch using the provided PSD. The website was designed using HTML &#038; CSS best practices.</h4>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Whole Bean Branding</title>
		<link>https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/case-studies/the-whole-bean-branding/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 23:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniel]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/?post_type=case_studies&#038;p=123</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The Whole Bean is a neighborhood coffee shop that needed help with branding and launching a website. I built The Whole Beans brand from the ground up including the development of brand psychology, user themes,[...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4>The Whole Bean is a neighborhood coffee shop that needed help with branding and launching a website. I built The Whole Beans brand from the ground up including the development of brand psychology, user themes, color theory, typography, social media headers, and custom icons and logos. I also provided them a PSD for their launch day landing page, which included a CTA form.</h4>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rogue Pickings</title>
		<link>https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/case-studies/rogue-pickings/</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 22:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniel]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/?post_type=case_studies&#038;p=102</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Rogue Pickings is a farm-to-table fresh food truck. I created a single page website from a provided PSD using HTML &#038; CSS best practices.]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4>Rogue Pickings is a farm-to-table fresh food truck. I created a single page website from a provided PSD using HTML &#038; CSS best practices.</h4>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Election Map</title>
		<link>https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/case-studies/election-map/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 20:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniel]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/?post_type=case_studies&#038;p=57</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[I built this interactive Election Map using an HTML map and custom CSS. Hovering over individual states triggers the results of that state and fills in the desired field with a vote count and announces[...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4>I built this interactive Election Map using an HTML map and custom CSS. Hovering over individual states triggers the results of that state and fills in the desired field with a vote count and announces the winner of the state.</h4>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Unplugged Music Magazine</title>
		<link>https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/case-studies/unplugged-music-magazine/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jan 2019 19:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Daniel]]></dc:creator>
		
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dksmith328.github.io/portfolio/?post_type=case_studies&#038;p=48</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Unplugged Music Magazine understands the importance of having a website that is built mobile-first as much of their users engage with their site on mobile devices. Taking an existing website, I was able to convert[...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h4>Unplugged Music Magazine understands the importance of having a website that is built mobile-first as much of their users engage with their site on mobile devices. Taking an existing website, I was able to convert the site into a visually pleasing and functional mobile site using HTML &#038; CSS best practices. </h4>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
